[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 3, "question": "And with the eyes of the world on the U.N. tonight, are Israel and the Palestinians getting closer to a deal?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "VBP", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NNPS", "VBG", "JJR", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 4, "answer": "Peace cannot be imposed on the parties.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["U.N."], "LOCATION": ["Israel"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "VBZ", ",", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 9, "question": "And how two presidents and a top fashion designer are working to rebuild a devastated nation?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 10, "answer": "What I'm saying is, to employee the people.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 25, "question": "What is your feeling about what may be going on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 26, "answer": "Well, there's a tremendous show of force here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "But tell me this from a legal point of view, when you studied everything to do with this case, what's your feeling about the original conviction of Troy Davis?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "It's a problematic case.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Troy Davis"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 87, "question": "What is the latest that's going on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "IN", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 88, "answer": "Indeed it is a very difficult time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "Do you believe that he's 100 percent innocent or do you simply believe there is enough doubt about the evidence that led to his conviction that should prevent an execution taking place?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "NN", "NN", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "Well, I think that both would be grounds for halting an execution.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 126, "question": "And I mean, do you know in terms of the practicalities of his evening, had he had his last meal and was he prepared for execution?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 127, "answer": "I do know that on the last time he received an execution warrant, he refused his last meal.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "110921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 137, "question": "Can I ask you, do you believe the death penalty is ever acceptable under any circumstances?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 138, "answer": "Well, as a Christian, as a man of faith, and because I believe of what -- because I believe in the best of America I am opposed to the death penalty.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "RB", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 160, "question": "What's their mood been like?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 161, "answer": "Well, of course they were completely overjoyed by the perspective that finally this was all over.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 168, "question": "Have they had to have any kind of medical treatment so far?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 169, "answer": "Yes, they seemed -- they seemed well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 175, "question": "Is that correct?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 176, "answer": "Well, these are the kind of things that I don't really want to speak upon the -- you know, the details of the release.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 180, "question": "Do they -- do they understand that they may have done that even if it was inadvertent?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 181, "answer": "Well, you'll probably have to ask them yourself.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "DT", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 187, "question": "How important was it to the two young men that their families were so determined to get them back and obviously tried everything they could to do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "DT", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "CC", "RB", "VBD", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 188, "answer": "This was a very, very important for them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["United Nations"], "TIME": ["this evening"], "PERSON": ["Abbas", "Obama"]}, "docId": "110921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 209, "question": "What is your understanding of how the meeting went with Mahmoud Abbas and the president?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 210, "answer": "Well, the President Abbas met with President Obama this evening and they exchanged views about the Palestinian decision to go to the United Nations to seek full membership at the international organization.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mahmoud Abbas"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNS", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 220, "question": "What do you really hope to achieve this week if you can?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "."], "aSentId": 221, "answer": "Well, actually what we are trying to achieve, we're trying to send a clear message to the international community that the current status quo that exist on the ground in the occupied Palestinian territories cannot continue.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Israel"]}, "docId": "110921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "CC", "IN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 243, "question": "How can you deliver a peace process if you don't have Hamas with you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 244, "answer": "Well, I think this is an issue that has been brought over and over again by Israel unfortunately to be used as a pretext not to move forward.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Hamas"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Friday"]}, "docId": "110921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 251, "question": "Do you sense that there's enough international world led by Barack Obama to get this done?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 252, "answer": "Well, I think if you are talking about from now until Friday that the Palestinian decision is very clear.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["United Nations"]}, "docId": "110921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 256, "question": "Could you do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 257, "answer": "Well, we have indicated that the day after we become a member of the United Nations, we will engage the Israelis in negotiations in order to resolve all the outstanding issues.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 275, "question": "How are you going to keep the republic?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 276, "answer": "I hope we're going to do it by, first of all, placing the future ahead of the present which is to say matching long-term means with ends.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 290, "question": "How do you respond to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 291, "answer": "Well, I think it's a little overstated.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$1.4 trillion"]}, "docId": "110921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "$", "CD", "CD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 303, "question": "A trillion dollars on wars?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 304, "answer": "Well, it didn't sound as big as it used to now that we're running $1.4 trillion every year.", "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["trillion dollars"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "DT", "JJS", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 321, "question": "Some of the answers?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 322, "answer": "I take the responsibility for often what I think are the best answers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["10 percent"]}, "docId": "110921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RBR", "IN", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 331, "question": "And where would you put it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 332, "answer": "Statistically if you were to repeal the tax cuts you'd solve less than 10 percent of the problem we have today.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 334, "question": "You wouldn't honestly look me in the eye and say that only 10 percent of the financial problems America has today are down to the Republicans, would you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VB", "IN", "RB", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "NNP", "VBZ", "NN", "VBP", "IN", "TO", "DT", "NNPS", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 335, "answer": "Well, that's a different question.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["10 percent"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", ":", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 355, "question": "What is your message to them as they continue to tear into Obama and make it all very partisan?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 356, "answer": "Yes, well, I have found in -- we have found in our state -- and I had to learn this the hard way, honestly -- that if you're interested in results, then you must always strive to bring people together.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 402, "question": "But do you personally believe in the death penalty?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 403, "answer": "I believe there are circumstances in which it is warranted.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "WP", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 410, "question": "If there can ever be doubt, why have it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "EX", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 411, "answer": "This is certainly what juries appear to be doing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 420, "question": "Any truth in this theory?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 421, "answer": "I'm not flirting with anything.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "NN", "CC", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 425, "question": "Do you have absolutely zero intention of ever being vice president?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "CD", "NN", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 426, "answer": "Yeah I have zero intention and zero expectation.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 429, "question": "If somebody asked you to be, would you say no?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "VB", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 430, "answer": "Well, I think that's something that a person ought not say.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 435, "question": "Would you say no if one of them asked you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "IN", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 436, "answer": "I can't tell you the answer to that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Haiti", "Haiti"]}, "docId": "110921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "TO", "VB", "CC", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 470, "question": "When you see what's happening in Haiti and the problems they've had, obviously caused by a very different natural disaster in their case, what advice would you give them about how you rebuild a country that's been through devastation?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WP", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 471, "answer": "Well, the first advice I would give the people of Haiti and the leadership in Haiti is not to despair and fear that they can't overcome the kinds of problems, however insurmountable they may seem.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Haiti"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "WRB", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 474, "question": "How important was the direct help from the United Nations?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "aSentId": 475, "answer": "That is helpful at the beginning mainly, when there is this kind of situation of emergency, where all kinds of help is needed.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["United Nations"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "NN", ",", "JJ", ",", "CC", "RB", ",", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 483, "question": "And how much more should the international community now be doing that perhaps they stopped doing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "JJ", "RBR", "MD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 484, "answer": "First of all, I must tell you we were really caught by surprise, for not having the culture of dealing with earthquake, first, and secondly, way before the earthquake, we had no infrastructure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 489, "question": "How much of that has been either wasted or, you know, lost through corruption or all the things that tend to happen in such a situation?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "VBN", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 490, "answer": "Well, that's exactly the point.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 498, "question": "From what you've seen in Haiti, what is the imperative now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 499, "answer": "If I could mention the imperative, what's always right in front of you.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Haiti"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBP", "VBN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 518, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 519, "answer": "These are horn bracelets.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 526, "question": "How are they responding to this kind of thing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 527, "answer": "You know, it's not as easy as I thought.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Rwanda"]}, "docId": "110921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 538, "question": "What do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 539, "answer": "First of all, the Rwanda model is a model that we are following very closely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 559, "question": "But is that necessarily a racist thing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 560, "answer": "It is a racist thing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]